class QuizQuestions {
  static Map<int, List<Map<String, dynamic>>> trueFalseQuestions = {
    1: [
      {'question': '1 x 2 = 2', 'isTrue': true, 'numericAnswer': 2},
      {'question': '1 x 4 = 2', 'isTrue': false, 'numericAnswer': 4},
      {'question': '1 x 6 = 6', 'isTrue': true, 'numericAnswer': 6},
      {'question': '1 x 8 = 8', 'isTrue': true, 'numericAnswer': 8},
      {'question': '1 x 10 = 11', 'isTrue': false, 'numericAnswer': 10},
      {'question': '1 x 7 = 8', 'isTrue': false, 'numericAnswer': 7},
      {'question': '1 x 9 = 9', 'isTrue': true, 'numericAnswer': 9},
      {'question': '1 x 3 = 1', 'isTrue': false, 'numericAnswer': 3},
      {'question': '1 x 5 = 5', 'isTrue': true, 'numericAnswer': 5},
      {'question': '1 x 12 = 13', 'isTrue': false, 'numericAnswer': 12},
    ],
    2: [
      {'question': '2 x 2 = 4', 'isTrue': true, 'numericAnswer': 4},
      {'question': '2 x 5 = 17', 'isTrue': false, 'numericAnswer': 10},
      {'question': '2 x 3 = 8', 'isTrue': false, 'numericAnswer': 6},
      {'question': '2 x 8 = 16', 'isTrue': true, 'numericAnswer': 16},
      {'question': '2 x 9 = 18', 'isTrue': true, 'numericAnswer': 18},
      {'question': '2 x 7 = 15', 'isTrue': false, 'numericAnswer': 14},
      {'question': '2 x 10 = 20', 'isTrue': true, 'numericAnswer': 20},
      {'question': '2 x 4 = 8', 'isTrue': true, 'numericAnswer': 8},
      {'question': '2 x 6 = 19', 'isTrue': false, 'numericAnswer': 12},
      {'question': '2 x 12 = 24', 'isTrue': true, 'numericAnswer': 24},
    ],
    3: [
      {'question': '3 x 2 = 6', 'isTrue': true, 'numericAnswer': 6},
      {'question': '3 x 4 = 13', 'isTrue': false, 'numericAnswer': 12},
      {'question': '3 x 6 = 18', 'isTrue': true, 'numericAnswer': 18},
      {'question': '3 x 8 = 26', 'isTrue': false, 'numericAnswer': 24},
      {'question': '3 x 10 = 30', 'isTrue': true, 'numericAnswer': 30},
      {'question': '3 x 7 = 22', 'isTrue': false, 'numericAnswer': 21},
      {'question': '3 x 11 = 33', 'isTrue': true, 'numericAnswer': 33},
      {'question': '3 x 14 = 43', 'isTrue': false, 'numericAnswer': 42},
      {'question': '3 x 15 = 45', 'isTrue': true, 'numericAnswer': 45},
      {'question': '3 x 9 = 44', 'isTrue': false, 'numericAnswer': 27},
    ],
    4: [
      {'question': '4 x 2 = 8', 'isTrue': true, 'numericAnswer': 8},
      {'question': '4 x 5 = 19', 'isTrue': false, 'numericAnswer': 20},
      {'question': '4 x 3 = 11', 'isTrue': false, 'numericAnswer': 12},
      {'question': '4 x 8 = 32', 'isTrue': true, 'numericAnswer': 32},
      {'question': '4 x 9 = 36', 'isTrue': true, 'numericAnswer': 36},
      {'question': '4 x 7 = 27', 'isTrue': false, 'numericAnswer': 28},
      {'question': '4 x 10 = 40', 'isTrue': true, 'numericAnswer': 40},
      {'question': '4 x 4 = 16', 'isTrue': true, 'numericAnswer': 16},
      {'question': '4 x 6 = 23', 'isTrue': false, 'numericAnswer': 24},
      {'question': '4 x 12 = 48', 'isTrue': true, 'numericAnswer': 48},
    ],
    5: [
      {'question': '5 x 2 = 15', 'isTrue': false, 'numericAnswer': 10},
      {'question': '5 x 4 = 20', 'isTrue': true, 'numericAnswer': 20},
      {'question': '5 x 3 = 20', 'isTrue': false, 'numericAnswer': 15},
      {'question': '5 x 8 = 40', 'isTrue': true, 'numericAnswer': 40},
      {'question': '5 x 9 = 40', 'isTrue': false, 'numericAnswer': 45},
      {'question': '5 x 7 = 30', 'isTrue': false, 'numericAnswer': 35},
      {'question': '5 x 10 = 50', 'isTrue': true, 'numericAnswer': 50},
      {'question': '5 x 4 = 25', 'isTrue': false, 'numericAnswer': 20},
      {'question': '5 x 6 = 30', 'isTrue': true, 'numericAnswer': 30},
      {'question': '5 x 12 = 60', 'isTrue': true, 'numericAnswer': 60},
    ],
    6: [
      {'question': '6 x 2 = 12', 'isTrue': true, 'numericAnswer': 12},
      {'question': '6 x 4 = 24', 'isTrue': true, 'numericAnswer': 24},
      {'question': '6 x 3 = 19', 'isTrue': false, 'numericAnswer': 18},
      {'question': '6 x 8 = 49', 'isTrue': false, 'numericAnswer': 48},
      {'question': '6 x 9 = 55', 'isTrue': false, 'numericAnswer': 54},
      {'question': '6 x 7 = 42', 'isTrue': true, 'numericAnswer': 42},
      {'question': '6 x 10 = 61', 'isTrue': false, 'numericAnswer': 60},
      {'question': '6 x 4 = 30', 'isTrue': false, 'numericAnswer': 24},
      {'question': '6 x 6 = 36', 'isTrue': true, 'numericAnswer': 36},
      {'question': '6 x 12 = 72', 'isTrue': true, 'numericAnswer': 72},
    ],
    7: [
      {'question': '7 x 2 = 15', 'isTrue': false, 'numericAnswer': 14},
      {'question': '7 x 4 = 27', 'isTrue': false, 'numericAnswer': 28},
      {'question': '7 x 3 = 22', 'isTrue': false, 'numericAnswer': 21},
      {'question': '7 x 8 = 57', 'isTrue': false, 'numericAnswer': 56},
      {'question': '7 x 9 = 63', 'isTrue': true, 'numericAnswer': 63},
      {'question': '7 x 7 = 49', 'isTrue': true, 'numericAnswer': 49},
      {'question': '7 x 10 = 70', 'isTrue': true, 'numericAnswer': 70},
      {'question': '7 x 11 = 36', 'isTrue': false, 'numericAnswer': 77},
      {'question': '7 x 6 = 42', 'isTrue': true, 'numericAnswer': 42},
      {'question': '7 x 12 = 84', 'isTrue': true, 'numericAnswer': 84},
    ],
    8: [
      {'question': '8 x 2 = 16', 'isTrue': true, 'numericAnswer': 16},
      {'question': '8 x 4 = 33', 'isTrue': false, 'numericAnswer': 32},
      {'question': '8 x 6 = 45', 'isTrue': false, 'numericAnswer': 48},
      {'question': '8 x 8 = 64', 'isTrue': true, 'numericAnswer': 64},
      {'question': '8 x 10 = 80', 'isTrue': true, 'numericAnswer': 80},
      {'question': '8 x 7 = 59', 'isTrue': false, 'numericAnswer': 56},
      {'question': '8 x 9 = 72', 'isTrue': true, 'numericAnswer': 72},
      {'question': '8 x 3 = 24', 'isTrue': true, 'numericAnswer': 24},
      {'question': '8 x 5 = 42', 'isTrue': false, 'numericAnswer': 40},
      {'question': '8 x 12 = 93', 'isTrue': false, 'numericAnswer': 96},
    ],
    9: [
      {'question': '9 x 2 = 18', 'isTrue': true, 'numericAnswer': 18},
      {'question': '9 x 4 = 35', 'isTrue': false, 'numericAnswer': 36},
      {'question': '9 x 6 = 55', 'isTrue': false, 'numericAnswer': 54},
      {'question': '9 x 8 = 72', 'isTrue': true, 'numericAnswer': 72},
      {'question': '9 x 10 = 90', 'isTrue': true, 'numericAnswer': 90},
      {'question': '9 x 7 = 62', 'isTrue': false, 'numericAnswer': 63},
      {'question': '9 x 9 = 81', 'isTrue': true, 'numericAnswer': 81},
      {'question': '9 x 3 = 28', 'isTrue': true, 'numericAnswer': 27},
      {'question': '9 x 5 = 42', 'isTrue': false, 'numericAnswer': 45},
      {'question': '9 x 12 = 104', 'isTrue': false, 'numericAnswer': 108},
    ],
    10: [
      {'question': '10 x 2 = 20', 'isTrue': true, 'numericAnswer': 20},
      {'question': '10 x 4 = 41', 'isTrue': false, 'numericAnswer': 40},
      {'question': '10 x 6 = 65', 'isTrue': false, 'numericAnswer': 60},
      {'question': '10 x 8 = 80', 'isTrue': true, 'numericAnswer': 80},
      {'question': '10 x 10 = 100', 'isTrue': true, 'numericAnswer': 100},
      {'question': '10 x 7 = 73', 'isTrue': false, 'numericAnswer': 70},
      {'question': '10 x 9 = 90', 'isTrue': true, 'numericAnswer': 90},
      {'question': '10 x 3 = 30', 'isTrue': true, 'numericAnswer': 30},
      {'question': '10 x 5 = 52', 'isTrue': false, 'numericAnswer': 50},
      {'question': '10 x 12 = 121', 'isTrue': false, 'numericAnswer': 120},
    ],
  };
}
